-Hey. -Hey. So, what do you think?
-嘿 -嘿，你覺得如何？
New haircut? Necklace? Dress?
新髮型？項鏈？洋裝？
Boots? Boots!
靴子？靴子！
Now, they're a little more than I usually spend on boots. Or rent.
它們比我平常買的靴子貴一點 也比租的貴
Did you say you bought "boots" or "boats"?
你說你買了「靴子」 還是「船」？
I know.
我知道
-I'll miss being able to afford food. -I'm sorry. They just looked so good.
-我會懷念買得起食物的日子 -對不起，它們真的很漂亮
The saleswoman was like:
專櫃小姐的表情像是在說
-"These are too expensive for you." -She had a point.
-「這些靴子太貴了，你買不起」 -她說的對
-Hey. -Hi. Oh, my God.
-嘿 -嗨，我的天啊
-Oh, Monica, those boots are amazing. -They're mine!
-摩妮卡，這雙靴子好漂亮喔 -它們是我的
-Too bad we're gonna have to return them. -Return them? They're gonna hear you.
-很遺憾我們得把它們退回去 -退回去？它們聽得見你說話
I'm not returning them. I know they cost a lot, but I'll wear them all the time.
我不會退回它們，我知道它們很貴 但我會常常穿著它們
You'll see. Besides, I love the compliments.
你會看到的 而且我喜歡聽到讚美
Have you ever had something so beautiful, everyone wants it?
你曾經擁有美到 大家都想擁有的東西嗎？
-I have you. -Nice try. I'm keeping the boots.
-我擁有你 -說的好，這靴子我留定了
The One With Monica's Boots
本集播出：摩妮卡的靴子
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
That's right. I love you.
沒錯，我愛你
And I'm gonna play with you all the time.
我會一直跟你玩
How can you let him talk to your crotch like that?
你怎麼能讓他對著你的胯下說話？
-He's talking to the baby. -Oh! Okay.
-他是在跟寶寶說話 -原來如此
Okay, because when he said, "l can't wait for your first words"..
好吧，因為當他說 「我等不及要聽到你說第一句話」…
I thought, "There's a trick."
我想「這招不錯」
Well, I gotta go, you guys. I'll see you later.
我得走了，待會見
-Okay. Bye. -Bye.
-好吧，拜拜 -拜
Hey, listen. Can you do me a favor? My sister knows you work at Ralph Lauren..
聽著，你能幫我一個忙嗎？ 我妹妹知道你在羅夫羅蘭工作…
Forget it. No way. I am not sending more Ralph Lauren clothes to prison.
算了，絕對不行 我不會再把羅夫羅蘭的衣服寄到監獄
-It is a waste. -No, not her.
-那是在暴殄天物 -不，不是她
My youngest sister, Dina, is interested in fashion.
我最小的妹妹蒂娜 對流行服裝很有興趣
She wants to talk to someone successful to give her some advice.
她想跟成功人士談談 給她一些建議
-I guess I could talk to my supervisors. -No, she wants to talk to you.
-我想我可以跟我的上司談一談 -不，她想跟你談
Really? Oh, my God. I'm successful.
真的嗎？天啊，我是成功人士
-Okay, so would you meet with her? -Yes, I'd love to. Have her come by.
-你能跟她見個面嗎？ -我很樂意，請她來找我吧
Great, thanks. You'll love her. She's the smartest of all the Tribbiani children.
天啊，謝謝，你會喜歡她的 她是崔比亞尼家最聰明的孩子
-Yeah, you know the SATs? -Yeah.
-你知道學術評量測驗嗎？ -知道
She took them.
她有考過
-Doesn't Ben go to Smithfield Day School? -Yeah. Why?
-班念的是史密斯菲德小學吧？ -對，怎麼了？
-Sting has a son that goes there too. -I know. He's in Ben's class.
-史汀有個兒子也在那裡唸書 -我知道，他跟班是同班同學
You knew and never said anything? With all the stupid dinosaur stuff you tell us?
你知道卻一直沒有告訴我們？ 你只跟我們說那些笨恐龍的事？
Fine, no more dinosaur stuff. Can I talk about fossils?
好吧，我不會再說恐龍的事 我能談談化石嗎？
"Sting's son,7 years old." And there's a picture.
「史汀七歲大的兒子」 還有他的照片
What are you reading, "The Kidnapper's Guide to Manhattan Private Schools"?
你在看什麼？ 「曼哈頓私立學校學童綁架指南」？
It's New York Magazine. It's an article about the city's best schools.
我在看《紐約雜誌》 報導城裡最棒的學校
-So how well do you know Sting? -I actually haven't even met him.
-你跟史汀很熟嗎？ -事實上我沒有見過他
Yeah. That's too bad. I really wanna go to his concert Friday, but it's sold out.
那真的很糟糕，我真的很想 去聽他星期五的演唱會，但票賣完了
I know! Why don't you meet him and get tickets.
我知道了 你為什麼不去跟他要票？
If you get two, I'll take you.
如果你可以要到兩張，我就帶你去
I'm picking Ben up tomorrow. Maybe he'll be there.
明天我會去接班 或許他會在那裡
There you go. You're so lucky. You might get to meet Sting tomorrow.
好吧，你真是幸運 明天你可能就會看到史汀了
That's why you have kids.
所以人一定要生小孩
-Hey, guys. -Hey.
-嗨，大伙們 -嘿
Hi, Monica. Hi, boots.
嗨，摩妮卡，嗨，靴子
See, Chandler? I'm getting a lot of use out of them already. They're very practical.
看吧？錢德，我常常穿它們 它們真的很實用
You can wear them with dresses, skirts, pants..
它們可以搭配 洋裝，裙子，長褲…
You wear them with shorts on the corner and earn the money to pay for them.
你可以穿著它們搭配短褲站在街角 賺點錢來付它們的帳單
-Wow, they're beautiful. -They hurt so much.
-哇，它們好漂亮 -它們真的很磨腳
-What? -The guy who made these..
-什麼？ -做這雙靴子的人…
hates feet and wants to see them die.
一定很討厭腳 想要看到它們死掉
Give them to me. I haven't felt my feet in years.
把它們送給我 我的腳好幾年沒有感覺了
I can't. I told Chandler I'd wear them all the time. I can't just give them away.
不行，我告訴錢德我會一直穿著它們 我不能把它們送人
-Then get your money back and return them. -I can't do that either.
-你可以拿去退貨換錢 -我也不能那麼做
The soles are scuffed up, and the insides are filled with my blood.
腳跟的地方有磨損 內襯沾滿了我的血
-Hey. -Hey, I just picked up Ben from school.
-嘿 -我剛剛去學校接班
I don't think you did a very thorough job.
你的任務還沒完成吧
I dropped him off at Carol's.
我把他送回卡蘿家了
Anyway, it turns out I'm not gonna get those tickets, though.
總之，我沒有要到門票
Oh, no. Why not?
不，為什麼？
It turns out Ben and Sting's son do not get along.
結果班跟史汀的兒子 處得不好
-How come? -Apparently, Sting's son made fun..
-怎麼會呢？ -很明顯地史汀的兒子取笑…
of the fact that Ben's moms are "lesbenims."
班的媽媽們是女同志
Wait. If they don't get along, smooth things over. Make them be friends.
等一下，如果他們處不好 幫他們勸和，讓他們做好朋友
-You can't force kids to be friends. -Sure you can.
-你不能逼孩子們做朋友 -當然可以
Give them some blocks. Put them in a playpen.
給他們一些積木 讓他們在遊戲床裡玩
-Playpen? Ben's 7. -Your kid is 7?
-遊戲床？班七歲了 -你的小孩七歲了？
He's really small.
他真的很矮喔！
-Please get the tickets. -I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
-拜託你去要門票 -抱歉，我辦不到
-Yes, you can. Sting says so himself. -What?
-不，你可以，史汀他自己說的 -什麼？
（羅斯可以）
Look, I'm sorry..
聽著，我很抱歉…
（羅斯可以）
Phoebe?
-菲比 -（羅斯可以幫我拿到門票）
（羅斯可以幫我拿到門票）
Here she is: future fashion superstar.
她來了，未來的流行界超級巨星
-Oh, Joey, I'm hardly.. -My little sister Dina.
-喬伊，我真的… -我的妹妹蒂娜
-Hi, Dina. Nice to meet you. -Hi.
-蒂娜，很高興見到你 -嗨
Thanks so much for meeting with me. Joey's told me so much about you.
謝謝你答應見我 喬伊告訴我很多關於你的事
This is so exciting for her.
她好興奮喔！
-Ralph Lauren smiled at her in the elevator. -You sure it was at you?
-羅夫羅蘭在電梯裡對她笑 -你確定嗎？
Because he likes it sometimes when the buttons light up.
因為他有時候看到電梯按鈕亮了 會開心微笑
Well, I'll let you two "fashists" get down to business.
我讓你們兩個「流行大師」 坐下來好好談正事
You, be good, learn a lot. And if she takes you to the freebie room, I need shirts..
你乖一點，好好聽話 如果她帶你去試衣間，我需要襯衫…
but none with that creepy logo with the guy riding the dog, holding the bone.
但我不要有個傢伙騎著狗 拿著骨頭的那一種
Okay. All right, Dina.
好吧，蒂娜
Well, let's talk about the different areas of fashion..
我們來談談 你可以考慮的…
that you could get involved in.
服裝界的不同領域
Let's see, there's design. But you may need a whole other degree for that.
讓我看看，有設計部門 但那得需要相關文憑
-Sales is great. You get to travel. -I don't care about fashion.
-銷售部門不錯，你可以旅行 -我不在乎流行服裝
I'm pregnant. And I know you are too, so you gotta help me.
我懷孕了，我知道你也是 你得幫幫我
Then there's marketing.
還有行銷部門
-What's wrong? -Nothing. I just was yawning.
-怎麼了？ -沒事，我只是在打哈欠
-Don't forget, my office party's tonight. -That's tonight?
-別忘了今晚我公司要辦派對 -是今晚嗎？
I forgot all about the "secret Santa" gift.
我忘了「神秘耶誕」禮物的事
Do we like this?
我們喜歡這個嗎？
We don't really have to go to this thing, do we?
我們今晚不一定要去 對吧？
I know that you don't like my office parties, but you can wear your new boots.
我知道你不喜歡參加我公司的派對 但你可以穿你的新靴子
See? Every cloud has a supple leather lining.
看吧？每件事都有它好的一面
-I don't wanna wear the boots tonight. -Why not?
-今晚我不想穿靴子 -為什麼？
I'm worried your bosses will see them and think they pay you too much money.
我擔心你老闆看到它們 會覺得他們給你的薪水太高了
Or your assistant will see them and want a raise.
或是你的助理看到它們 會要求加薪
Do you think I work some kind of boot-pricing company?
你以為我是在 幫靴子訂價的公司上班嗎？
I picked out this outfit I wanna wear, and the boots don't go with it.
我已經挑好了我要穿的衣服 靴子跟它不配
You said those boots go with skirts, dresses and pants.
你說過這雙靴子 可以搭配裙子、洋裝跟長褲
What are you planning on wearing, a chicken suit?
你打算穿什麼？ 母雞裝嗎？
Fine. If you want me to, I'll wear the boots.
好吧，如果你要的話 我會穿靴子
In fact, I'll go into my room right now and try the outfit on.
事實上我要到臥室去 試穿我的衣服
Christmas party in my boots!
穿著我的靴子參加耶誕節派對
I can't go in there. I can't tell him.
我不能進去，我不敢告訴他
It's gonna be okay. He has been incredibly supportive of me.
一定會沒事的 他一直都非常支持我
And if he gets a little upset, that's what the meatball sub is for.
如果他大發脾氣 快把肉餅潛艇三明治拿給他
-Thank you. -Okay.
-謝謝 -好吧
Hey! It's my fashion girls.
我的流行界女王們回來了
-What's wrong? -Why don't you sit down.
-怎麼了？ -你為什麼不坐下呢？
Dina has something that she wants to tell you.
蒂娜有件事 想告訴你
What's going on? Is it Mom? Is she sick?
發生了什麼事？ 是媽媽嗎？她生病了嗎？
Is it Dad's heart?
是爸爸的心臟嗎？
Is that a sandwich?
那是三明治嗎？
-Mom and Dad are fine. -Is that a sandwich?!
-媽媽跟爸爸沒事 -那是三明治嗎？
Joey, there's something that you should know. Dina?
喬伊，有件事你得知道 蒂娜
-I'm pregnant. -What?
-我懷孕了 -什麼？
Now. Give him the sandwich!
快給他三明治
Obviously, this is a mistake. You can't be pregnant.
很明顯地這是個誤會 你不可能懷孕
Because you have to have sex to get pregnant.
因為你得先做愛 才會懷孕
Joe, I tried to wait until I was 25, like you did.
喬伊，我試著學你一樣 等到25歲再嘗禁果
What? Dina..
什麼？蒂娜…
I can't believe this. You're the good one. You went to college! Both years!
我不敢相信，你是個好孩子 你念過大學，還念了兩年
Who did this to you?
是誰幹的？
Bobby Corso. But he's a real nice guy. I like him a lot. He's real funny.
巴比科索，但他是個很好的人 我很喜歡他，他很好笑
You got pregnant for "funny"? Dina, if he's funny, laugh!
你因為「好笑」而懷孕？ 蒂娜，如果他很好笑，你只要笑就行了
-I'll be back. Stay here! -Why? Where you going?
-我馬上回來，你留在這裡 -為什麼？你要去哪裡？
I can't look at you right now.
我現在沒辦法看你
I know.
我知道
Oh, there you are, Ben.
你在這裡啊，班
You're Ben, right?
你是班，對吧？
Aunt Phoebe, what are you doing here?
菲比阿姨，你來這裡做什麼？
I heard you're having a problem with one of the boys.
我聽說 你跟一個同學處不好
So I thought I'd come and sit you both down, have a little talk and make it all okay.
我想來幫你們冷靜下來 好好地談一談，解決所有問題
Now, the boy's name is Sting's son.
那個孩子叫做史汀的兒子
Jack? I hate him. He's a jerk.
傑克？我恨他，他是個混蛋
Sometimes people may seem like jerks on the outside..
有時候人們 外表看起來像是混蛋…
but they have famous fathers.
但他們有個名人爸爸
I have to go. My friend Doug is waiting for me over there.
我得走了 我朋友道格在等我
Wow, your friend Doug looks a lot like Billy Joel.
你朋友道格 長得好像比利喬
-Is that who his father is? -No. His dad's a dentist.
-他是他的爸爸嗎？ -不，他爸爸是牙醫
Him, you're friends with.
你跟他做朋友？
-Excuse me, can I help you with something? -Yes. I'm looking for Jack's parents.
-對不起，需要我幫忙嗎？ -對，我在找傑克的父母
-Are you with one of the students? -I'm with Ben.
-你是家長嗎？ -我來找班
-Are you one of Ben's mothers? -I am one of Ben's mothers.
-你是班的媽媽？ -我是班的媽媽
I'm a lesbian.
我是女同志
It was difficult coming out to my parents.
我爸媽 很難接受這種事
Well, hi. I'm Jenny Boon. I'm a new teacher here.
嗨，我是珍妮布恩 我是新來的老師
-I've only met your partner, Carol. -That would make me Susan.
-我只見過你的另一半卡蘿 -那麼我就是蘇珊
Right. Are you looking for Jack's parents to discuss his problems with Ben?
對，你要找傑克父母 討論他跟班的問題嗎？
I think the parents should sit down together and have a conversation.
我想父母們應該坐下來 好好談一談
Yeah, let's do that!
對，我們就那麼辦吧
That sounds good.
聽起來很不錯
We should sit down and talk. Me, my lover, Carol, and the Stings.
我們應該坐下來談一談 我，我的愛人卡蘿跟史汀夫婦
-How will I get in touch with them? -Their number's on the contact sheet.
-我要怎麼聯絡他們？ -聯絡簿上有他們的電話號碼
Could I get a copy of that? Carol threw it out. She lost ours.
我能影印一份嗎？ 卡蘿把它丟了，她弄丟了我們的聯絡簿
She's such a scatterbrain. But, man, what a hot piece of ass.
她真的很糊塗 但天啊，她的屁股真的很好看
-You know, that party wasn't bad. -Yeah. I didn't know there'd be dancing.
-那場派對還不錯 -對，我不知道還有舞會
That was a fun surprise.
那是個大驚喜
-I don't see a cab. Maybe we should walk. -No, we can't walk.
-我看不到計程車，或許我們該走路 -不，我們不能走路
No. Hey, there's a cab.
不，有計程車
That's a police car.
那是警車
Maybe we could commit a crime, have them pick us up.
或許我們該犯個法 讓他們來逮捕我們
-It's 15 blocks to the subway. Come on. -Okay.
-離地鐵站只有15條街遠，來吧 -好吧
Do you think we can get to the subway if we climb through that manhole?
你想我們可以從那個下水道孔 直接掉到地鐵站裡嗎？
-What's going on? -I can't walk, okay?
-什麼事不對勁嗎？ -我走不動了，好嗎？
-These boots were a huge mistake. -What?
-買這雙靴子是個天大的錯誤 -什麼？
You were right. I never should have bought them. They're killing me, one toe at a time.
你說的對，我不該買下它們 它們害我的腳好痛，我的腳趾快斷了
-So they're really tight, huh? -I just said you were right, sweetie.
-它們真的很緊嗎？ -我只是說你說的對，甜心
Isn't it clear I'm delirious from the pain?
你看不出來我痛到快發瘋了嗎？
So I was right. This is what it feels like to be right.
我說的對 感覺才是最重要的
It's oddly unsettling.
我為什麼覺得很不安？
How are we gonna we get home? Maybe a piggyback ride?
我們要怎麼回家？ 我們來玩騎馬打仗吧
I don't think me getting on your back is gonna improve matters.
我不認為讓你來背我 能改善現在的情況
Wow, being right sure doesn't help with the funny.
實事求事的態度 一點都不好玩
-Hop on. -Okay, wait.
-來吧 -好吧，等一下
Let me just get my boots off first.
我先把靴子脫掉
Oh, God.
天啊
I know you're in pain right now, but I'm a little turned-on.
我知道你很痛 但我有點心癢癢的
Do you ever worry that you'll be walking and your baby will just slip out?
你會不會擔心走路的時候 寶寶會掉出來？
What college was that, Dina?
你念哪所大學的？蒂娜
Oh, my God. Bobby?
天啊，巴比
Hi, Dina. Good to see you.
蒂娜，很高興能見到你
-Joey, what are you doing? -Just what needs to be done.
-喬伊，你在做什麼？ -我只是在做我該做的事
-Dearly beloved, we're gathered here.. -This is crazy.
-親愛的親友們，我們齊聚一堂… -這太瘋狂了
Don't interrupt me when I'm talking to God!
我在跟上帝說話 別打斷我
-Where were we? Do you take this man..? -No!
-我們說到哪裡了？你願意嫁這個人… -不
-You'll take him. -No, I won't!
-你得嫁他 -不，我不會的
-You don't get a say. -Yes, I do.
-你沒有權利說話 -不，我有
-I heard "l do." We're halfway there. You. -All right, Joey, that is enough!
-我聽到了，已經完成一半，再來是你 -好吧，喬伊，夠了
As beautiful and moving as this ceremony is, this is not legal.
雖然這個婚禮既漂亮又溫馨 這是不合法的
They don't have a marriage license or witnesses, and the groom only has one shoe.
他們沒有結婚證書或證婚人 而且新郎只穿一隻鞋
Yeah, he took the other one off and hit me with it.
對，他把另一隻鞋脫了 用它來打我
What am I supposed to do?
我該怎麼辦？
You're supposed to realize they are adults and that can make their own decisions.
你應該瞭解他們是成年人 可以自己做決定
No, they can't. They were stupid enough to get knocked up!
不，他們不能 他們笨到讓自己懷孕
Contraceptives are not always effective. Right?
預防措施不一定有效 對吧？
-Yeah. We kind of didn't use any. -Come on, kids, a little help here!
-對，我們沒有做預防措施 -孩子們，幫幫我吧
Wow! This place is incredible!
這個地方真的很棒
Sting's pen..
史汀的筆…
that he gave to Phoebe.
他送給了菲比
Come on, secret passageway.
來吧，秘密通道
-Hi. -Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
I'm Trudie. You must be Ben's mum.
我是楚蒂，你一定是班的媽媽
-Why else would I be here? -Why don't you sit down.
-不然我為什麼要到這裡來呢？ -請坐
I gather Jack and Ben haven't been getting along lately.
我知道傑克跟班 最近處得不太好
I'm sure there are two sides to this story.
我相信這個故事一定有兩面說法
But all I've heard is that Ben's a bit of a "poo-poo-head."
但我聽到的是 班是個「大笨蛋」
-I'm sorry, won't Jack's father be joining us? -No.
-抱歉，傑克的爸爸不會來嗎？ -不會
I see. You see, I think it would be better for the children..
我懂了，我覺得 如果父母都能來…
if all the parents were here. Except for, you know, Ben's birth mother and father.
對孩子們比較好 但班的生母跟爸爸除外
Well, I'm sorry. Jack's father's not available.
對不起 傑克的爸爸沒空
Okay. Well, then, could we reschedule for Friday night, perhaps at 8:00?
好吧，我們可以再約 星期五晚上八點見嗎？
No, I know that wouldn't work. My husband's in concert.
不，我想那是行不通的 我丈夫要辦演唱會
Concert. Yeah. That does put us in quite a pickle.
演唱會，對 那讓問題變得有點棘手
I'm busy before and after the concert, and he's obviously busy during.
演唱會前後我都有事 演唱會的時間他又很忙
So I guess you and I should talk about Jack and Ben right now.
我想你跟我 現在該來談談傑克跟班的事
Unless.. Unless..
除非…
Okay, I would be willing to go to the concert..
我願意到演唱會上…
all the while thinking about the children.
想一想孩子們的事
-Are you here for tickets? -Thank you. Four would be great.
-你是來要票的嗎？ -謝謝，四張就夠了
I'm not giving concert tickets to someone who'd use their son like this.
我不會把演唱會門票 送給這樣利用自己孩子的人
Then you're in luck. Ben's not my son.
那正好，班不是我的兒子
Look, I've just pressed a button triggering a silent alarm.
聽著，我已經按下 靜聲警鈴
-Any minute now, the police will be here. -The Police? Here?
-警察隨時會到 -《警察合唱團》要來？
A reunion?
他們要復合了？
Okay,10 blocks down. Five to go.
好吧，已經走了十條街，只剩五條
-Oh, wait! Stop, stop! -Oh, I'm sorry. Do you need a break?
-等一下，停 -抱歉，你需要休息嗎？
My boots in tan! Can you get a little closer so I see the price?
是米色的靴子，你能靠近一點 讓我看看價錢嗎？
I can see it from right here. It'll cost you one husband.
我在這裡就看到了 它會害得你丟掉一個老公
I'm sorry. I can walk the rest of the way now. Just give me my boots.
抱歉，我可以自己走了 把我的靴子還給我
-I don't have your boots. -I don't have them either. Where are they?
-我沒有拿你的靴子 -我也沒拿，它們在哪裡？
Why don't you check in one of my saddlebags while I chew on a bale of hay?
你為什麼不看看馬鞍？ 我先去吃點草
Okay. My God, we gotta go back and get them!
好吧，天啊 我們得回去找靴子
Are you ever gonna wear the boots again?
你會再穿那雙靴子嗎？
Yes, I am. Okay? They're very practical.
我會的，好嗎？它們很實用
-I could wear them with pants or skirts.. -Honey. Honey.
-我可以搭配長褲或裙子… -老婆
Okay, I'll never wear them again. I just didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
好吧，我再也不會穿它們 我只是沒機會跟它們說再見
You know what? You can say goodbye to the tan ones.
你知道嗎？ 你可以跟米色的靴子說再見
-Okay. All right. -Okay.
-好吧 -好吧
Bye, boots. Wait! Half off!
再見，靴子，等一下，打五折
Just because they're not getting married doesn't mean it's a disaster.
他們沒結婚 不代表那是世界末日
-Maybe they have a plan. -Oh, okay, let's hear their plan.
-或許他們有計劃 -好吧，我們聽聽他們的計劃
Now, what's the future look like for Dina and Bobby?
蒂娜跟巴比 會有什麼樣的未來？
Well..
這個嘛…
I really have high hopes for my band.
我對我的樂團寄望很高
-You were right. He is funny. -Now, wait a minute.
-你說的對，他是很好笑 -等一下
I bet when you told people you wanted to be an actor, they laughed at you.
我敢說你一開始告訴大家你要當演員 大家都笑你
Come on, Bobby, tell us a little bit about your band.
來吧，巴比 跟我們談談你的樂團
Well, it's just me and my pal Rooster. The band's name is Numbnuts.
團員只有我跟我朋友魯斯特 樂園名自叫做《呆瓜》
Really?
真的嗎？
If you're having a baby, you should be married.
如果你要生孩子 你應該結婚
Even if it is to Bobby. Dude, that's not a compliment.
即使是嫁給巴比 我不是在誇獎你
-I knew you wouldn't be supportive. -So, what are you gonna do?
-我就知道你不會支持我 -你打算怎麼辦？
Have the baby and raise it by yourself? Without a husband?
你要自己帶大孩子？ 沒有丈夫幫你？
You can't be a single mother alone! You're gonna ruin your life!
你沒辦法當單親媽媽 你會毀了自己的一生
-Excuse me. Am I ruining my life? -No, it's different for you.
-對不起，我毀了我的一生嗎？ -不，你不一樣
You're so strong. You're not some dumb kid who doesn't know what she's doing.
你很堅強 你不是不知道自己在做什麼的笨小孩
-Excuse me? -One pregnant woman at a time, please!
-你說什麼？ -我一次只能跟一個孕婦說話
I just want you to be okay.
我只是希望你過得好
So forcing her to marry Bobby is gonna make that happen?
逼她嫁給巴比 她就會過的好嗎？
Maybe.
或許吧
Yeah. So, what kind of music does Numbnuts..?
對，《呆瓜》的音樂是什麼類型的…
Oh, forget it! I can't!
算了，我辦不到
I am scared to death about this. But I think I can do it. I just need some help.
我真的很害怕 但我想我辦得到，我只是需要幫助
-Bobby's gonna be here the whole time. -You bet I am.
-巴比會一直陪著我 -沒錯
And to answer your earlier question, we're straight-up gangster rap.
至於你剛剛問的那個問題 我們唱純黑幫饒舌歌
Look, Rachel's told me how much easier you've made all this on her.
瑞秋告訴我 你一直都很支持她
-Why can't you do that for me? -Because you're my baby sister!
-你為什麼不能支持我？ -因為你是我的妹妹
And you're my big brother. You're my favorite guy in the whole world.
你是我哥哥 你是我全世界最喜歡的人
I'm not even scared to tell Mom and Dad. I was scared of telling you.
我甚至不怕告訴媽媽跟爸爸 我害怕告訴你
I'd be scared of them, but all right.
我也會怕他們，但好吧
I can't stand the thought of having this baby with you mad at me.
想到你會因為我懷孕而生我的氣 我就受不了
I want him to have his uncle.
我要他有舅舅
Is my baby gonna have his Uncle Joey?
我的寶寶會有喬伊舅舅嗎？
Of course he's gonna have his Uncle Joey.
他當然會有喬伊舅舅
We'll be all right. Even if we're not married, this baby will be so loved.
我們會沒事的，即使我們沒結婚 寶寶還是會得到寵愛
-And not just by us. -That's right.
-不只是我們會愛他 -沒錯
By his uncle too.
他的舅舅也會愛他
And by you.
還有你
Bobby, why don't we come over here and let them have a little moment, okay?
巴比，我們為什麼不過來這裡 讓他們獨處一下？
Come here.
過來
No, seriously, what's wrong with you?
不，說真的，你到底有什麼問題？
Guess what.
你猜怎麼了
We're good. We're good. We know each other.
沒事 我們認識
So..
所以…
-anyway, guess what. -Oh, there's more?
-總之你猜怎麼了 -還有嗎？
You're gonna love me so much. I got Sting tickets!
你一定會很愛我 我弄到史汀的門票了
Oh, my God, I do love you! How did you do it?
天啊，我真的愛你 你怎麼辦到的？
Well, let's just say:
就說
（羅斯可以）
-Where are the seats? -Middle balcony.
-座位是哪一區？ -在中間包廂
Would you say that's more than 50 yards away..
我們的位置 離史汀，他太太…
from Sting, his wife or a member of his family?
跟他的家人 超過50碼嗎？
-Yeah. -Then that's not breaking the law. I'm there!
-對 -那樣就不犯法，我會去